I made a big mistake by going to the water park today.
Riya was wanting to go to the water park for a long time.
So I thought
we should leave today before the water park closes.
And this is our makeup box
which has been ruined by Riya.  Then what,
we sat in our car and
left for our destination.  Then when we
reached the water park, after getting our entry, we
looked around and the view here was different.  And
after wearing the dress here, it
felt different because I have never worn such dresses before.
And brother,
I was scared after seeing such high swings.
But son said today I will swing you on all the swings only then I will leave and
we started from the pool
and look at Riya's father,
lying on the velvet mattress, her father is enjoying more than Riya
and first of all Jatin
took me with him on this swing but today
I realized that the children whose hands
I used to swing, today they are swinging me.
Then we had so much fun with the children that
we also became children and look at Riya who was
so scared earlier, now she is swinging alone.
And then I also got courage.
So I told his father to come along.
But as soon as we came down from the slide,
a brother came in front of us, so we took him
along too.  That's why I'm afraid of swings.
These memories will remain with us and
when we watch this video, we will definitely laugh.
Radhe Radhe.